(Leonard:)Where is everything?
(Sheldon:)In my present,
it's in the future.
(Sheldon:)In your present,
it's been crammed in the bedroom
(Sheldon:)by an enterprising young man
(Sheldon:)I met in The Home Depot
parking lot.
(Leonard:)I know what you're doing.
(Leonard:)You're trying to get attention
so we'll feel bad for you,
(Leonard:)but it's not happening.
(Sheldon:)No, what I'm doing
is trying to figure out
(Sheldon:)how to live my life now
that everyone is leaving me.
(Leonard:)Will you knock it off?
We're across the hall.
(Sheldon:)As the kids are saying today,
"talk to the hand."
(Penny:)They're not saying that.
(Sheldon:)They are in 2003.
(Penny:)No, they're really not.
♪ Thor and Dr. Jones ♪
♪ One runs from Loki ♪
♪ The other runs from stones. ♪
(Raj(singing):)So, what do you think?
(Emily:)Wow.
(Raj:)Runs from stones means
that-that big boulder,
(Raj:)but I couldn't rhyme anything
with boulder.
(Emily:)Colder, shoulder,